santiventures.com 2010-03-30

# Santiventures.com. Profitable ventures that do work 24/7

| 

### Privacy Policy

Santiventures, respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security.

We know that you are concerned with how your personal and financial information is treated. This Privacy Policy sets forth our current policies and demonstrates our commitment to your financial privacy. Please bear in mind, however, that we may change the content or services found on our Web site, and consequently, our privacy policy at any time in the future. Please revisit this page from time to time to be sure that you are familiar with any changes to our policy. Your continued use of our web site following any modifications to this privacy policy will be conclusively deemed acceptance of any changes. Santiventures, is committed to safeguarding the personal information you provide us. This privacy policy describes how we handle and protect personal information we collect about individuals who apply for or receive our products and services. The provisions of this notice apply to former customers as well as our current customers.

We collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service.

* * *

### Protection Of Your Personal Information 

We maintain personal information in a password-protected electronic file outside of our Web site or its servers, and we limit access to such information to employees who need to have such information to provide services to you. We will only use such information about you to verify your identity and eligibility to receive certain products or services, to provide information to you about products and services that we believe may be of interest to you, to record your interest in products and services that we offer, and to respond to your requests for information.

Our employees are required to maintain and protect the confidentiality of your personal information and must follow established procedures to do so. We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. We do not rent or sell your name or personal information to anyone.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by members area management. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error or you can make necessary changes yourself if allowed by the system. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

By making your deposit with Santiventures, you declare that you have read, understood, and accepted our Privacy Policy and our Terms Of Use. 

|    
|   
---  

###  _Secure SSL version_

### _Members quotes_

_"I was searching for a profitable way to invest money and I found it with Santi Ventures. They fulfilled my expectations and helped to earn extra money I just needed badly to pay off my mortgage. Thanks " , Chris J._
